{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Are you going to the show? \"No, the tickets are _________ for me.\"",
      "a": "so much expensive",
      "b": "terrible expensive",
      "c": "enough expensive",
      "d": "far too expensive",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Much/far/ rather/a little/a bit/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj \n+ Too adj (for sbd) to do sth",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The lady on the ground looked dead but the faint pulse proved that she was still ___.",
      "a": "life",
      "b": "live",
      "c": "lively",
      "d": "alive",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Alive(adj): still living and not dead",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The two boys look exactly ___.",
      "a": "alike",
      "b": "same",
      "c": "same ones",
      "d": "like",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- An adverb is also a modifier, but it describes a verb, an adjective, or another adverb \n- An adverb modifying an adjective will often answer \"how\" or \"to what extent\" for adjectives \n- Alike (adj): very similar",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The American dream does not come to those who fall _________.",
      "a": "sleep",
      "b": "sleeping",
      "c": "slept",
      "d": "asleep",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Fall asleep: \n+ To begin to sleep \n+ Used to mean that someone dies, when you want to avoid saying this directly",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Of all the employees Henry is _________ one for the position and the task.",
      "a": "the most suitable",
      "b": "the most fit",
      "c": "most suitable",
      "d": "the fitter",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Superlative comparison: The + (Most) Superlative Adjectives (+ noun) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How about Tracy? \"She arrived there ___\"",
      "a": "safely",
      "b": "safe",
      "c": "with safeness",
      "d": "with safety",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": ".\n- An adverb is also a modifier, but it describes a verb, an adjective, or another adverb\n+ \"Safely\" describes \"arrive\"\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The clerk said that it didn't need ___ paperwork.",
      "a": "lots of",
      "b": "many",
      "c": "much",
      "d": "a great deal of",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Much+ uncountable noun (paperwork) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This study proves that there is no life on the Venus. \"But ___ astronomers still think there is.\"",
      "a": "much",
      "b": "a great deal",
      "c": "many a",
      "d": "a great many",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Much+ uncountable noun \n- Many + countable noun (astronomers) \n- Great many= A great deal of ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How ___ can you finish the measuring?",
      "a": "long",
      "b": "often",
      "c": "many",
      "d": "soon",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ".\n- Soon: \t in a short time from now, or a short time after something else happens",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The situation sounds ___.",
      "a": "well",
      "b": "good",
      "c": "to be well",
      "d": "to be good",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Verb of appearance : (feel, taste, smell, sound, look, appear, and seem)+ Adjective : modifies the noun before the verb",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "7",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}